worldtimezone.com 2007-12-10

# Web Site Disclaimer and Privacy Statement for WorldTimeZone.com

|  TIME ZONES and CONTAINED REGIONS/AREAS  
  
---  
-12 | -11 | -10 | -9 | -8 | -7 | -6 | -5 | -4 | -3 | -2 | -1 | 0 | +1 | +2 | +3 | +4 | +5 | +6 | +7 | +8 | +9 | +10 | +11 | +12  
M|Y | X | W | V | U | T | S | R | Q | P | O | N | Z | A | B | C | D | E | F | G | H | I | K | L | M|Y  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
Web Site Disclaimer and Privacy Statement  
Thank you for visiting the WorldTimeZone.com web site and reviewing our Disclaimer and Privacy statement. Disclaimer  
The information on this free web site is provided on "as is" basis without warranty of any kind.  
WorldTimeZone.com takes absolutely no responsibility for any errors on this free web site. You use the information on your own risk.   
  
---  
Personal Information  
No personal information is collected by WorldTimeZone.com from visitors to our website, when viewing pages, or when navigating WorldTimeZone.com. We also do not collect or harvest the email addresses of people who email us directly. We only use them to respond to your queries.  
  
Advertisers and Cookies  
**WorldTimeZone.com cannot guarantee the content and/or availability of advertiser's products and services or be held responsible for any sweepstakes, sweepstakes results or banner ad which may award prizes.  
Users who participate in these activities do so at their own risk and must work directly with the advertiser to claim any award. **

WorldTimeZone.com itself does not use cookies. WorldTimeZone.com works with third parties that serves ads to this site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by those ads companies, and WorldTimeZone.com does not have access to or control over this information.  
  
Information Collected and Stored Automatically  
Our host server provider will automatically gather and store some information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally but does enable us to track the usage of our web site and its accessibility. This information includes:  

  1. The date and time you accessed our site; 
  2. The type of browser and operating system used to access our site; 
  3. The Internet domain name; 
  4. The pages you visited; 
  5. If you linked to our web site from another web site, the address of that web site (i.e. a Search Engine or link from another web site) 

We use this information to help make our site more useful to visitors and to learn more about the number of visitors to our site, how they found our site and the type of technology that they are using.   
  
Links To Other Sites  
Our web site has links to other web sites. WorldTimeZone.com is not responsible for the privacy practices, actions, or content of such other sites. It is the responsibility to the web surfer to evaluate the content and usefulness of information obtained from other sites.   
  
Questions? Corrections?  
If you have any questions, please contact us via Email.  

Absolutely briliant web site. Since my familiy is scattered all over the globe, it makes it easier not to disturb them sleeping. As well very helpful making professional telephone calls. Keep it up!   
Tishina  
[ Frankfurt ](http://www.worldtimezone.com/time/wtzresult.php?CiID=6419&forma=24h), Germany [ [ Reading ](http://www.worldtimezone.com/time/wtzresult.php?CiID=11775&forma=24h), United Kingdom ]   
  
---  
  
I always had a tough time to look around but with the help of this site, its been very very easy for me to get into any of the world and look up for the time etc.. Its fablous, interesting and gets to know lots out of it and gets knowledge. God bless the person who did come up with such an idea.   
John Rey  
[ Bhutan ](http://www.worldtimezone.com/time/wtzresult.php?CiID=42108&forma=24h), [ Bhutan ]   
  
This site is great. My coworkers and I use it regularly as we have to make phone calls all across the US and Canada. It is very helpful in assuring that we do not call anyone at an unreasonable time. Thank you so much for such a useful tool.   
Jonny Collins  
[ Lewiston ](http://www.worldtimezone.com/time/wtzresult.php?CiID=9003&forma=12h), Maine, USA [ [ Lewiston](http://www.worldtimezone.com/time/wtzresult.php?CiID=9003&forma=12h), Maine, USA]   
  
Global System for Mobile communications (GSM)\- most popular standard for Mobile phones in the world. GSM service is used in more than 210 countries and territories.

|  |   
---|---|---  
  
| 

  Europe  
  Asia/Middle East  
  N.America/Caribbean

| 

  55 countries  
  08 countries  
  11 countries

| 

  South America  
  Australia/Oceania  
  Africa

| 

  05 countries  
  04 countries  
  03 countries  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
 |   
|    Time Abbreviations    |  | VIEW  
---|---|---  
  
|  |     What time is it in:    |  | VIEW  
---|---|---  
  
* [ INTERACTIVE TIME MAP](http://www.worldtimezone.com/time/interactive-time-map.php) provides you an at-a-glance view of your local time in relation to 19 worldwide locations. Simply select your location, the date and time you want for your event, and let the Interactive Time Map do the rest.
* [ MEETING PLANNER / CALL PLANNER](http://www.worldtimezone.com/time/wtzplanner.php) \- The International Call Planner enables you to chose TIME ZONE and multiple locations of your choice and identify the best time for your meeting in relation to your location.
